<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>grimoire on Morgan Mayday</title>
    <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in grimoire on Morgan Mayday</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://morganmay.day/grimoire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>but, instead, something else.</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/but-instead-something-else/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/but-instead-something-else/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Required reading: &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood&#34;&gt;Not A Person&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Search. if not a person, then what?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;you could go the route of the dolls. could disavow personhood, crunch down on your agency, be an object acted upon, rather than an actor in your own right. you could be a tool, an implement, something in service of another. it&amp;rsquo;d be safer, easier, comfier, being provided for like that and providing in turn, as required of you. you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t even have to be a person. someone else can do the heavy bit. you can interface with Consensus with an intermediary, rather than direct.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>killjoy</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/killjoy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/killjoy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;people in real life: hey man hows it going&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;various (meme)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a tendency to assign neutrality to the masculine form of words in English, mostly in slang&amp;ndash;&amp;ldquo;hey, man,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;hey, dude,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;king shit&amp;rdquo;&amp;ndash;though it shows up sometimes in general phrasing still, feminist pushes mostly have made things like &amp;ldquo;fireman&amp;rdquo; over &amp;ldquo;firefighter&amp;rdquo; obsolete. This is, overall, something most people do, and something most people find pretty harmless. A lot of people will go through their lives not thinking about it, or thinking about it a tiny bit at most.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>how to be a transmisogynist</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/htt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/htt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is critical satire, and does not have content warnings. Caveat emptor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Inspired in part by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.auramgold.com/essays/abusers-guide&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So you&amp;rsquo;ve met someone, and you think they might be a trans woman&amp;ndash;maybe they&amp;rsquo;ve said as much, maybe they haven&amp;rsquo;t, but you&amp;rsquo;ve &lt;em&gt;decided&lt;/em&gt; that they&amp;rsquo;re in&amp;hellip;however you define that category. You&amp;rsquo;ve got a couple options!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The easiest and simplest way to be transmisogynist is to refuse to recognize their womanhood. He/him and it/its can get you Cancelled, here in 2026, but of course they/them is an acceptable substitute, and your victim du jour can&amp;rsquo;t really tell you off for it without looking like a lunatic SJW male. A key note is to &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; it/its a trans woman who actually wants those pronouns, you&amp;rsquo;ll look stupid, or even worse&amp;ndash;&lt;em&gt;accepting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Read, Perchance to Dream</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dreaming-a-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dreaming-a-self/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read this piece in good faith, or not at all.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Who are you, when the lights are out and nobody&amp;rsquo;s watching?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve been in broader plural circles before, adjacent at all to what we call &amp;ldquo;pop plur&amp;rdquo;, you&amp;rsquo;ve met fictives, generally of characters from media. This is something some people&amp;ndash;or rather, some People&amp;ndash;judge plural folk as &lt;em&gt;lesser&lt;/em&gt; as a whole for. This is also adjacent to the endo/exo divide as a concept: systems saying &amp;ldquo;well, &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; have a reason to be like this, but they don&amp;rsquo;t so they&amp;rsquo;re not real/worthy of respect, they&amp;rsquo;re doing it for internet points.&amp;rdquo; Respectability politics is an unwinnable game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>notes on perfectionism</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/perfectionism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/perfectionism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;this is notes. loose stuff. don&amp;rsquo;t try to find a beam in here, this is stream of thought.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I talk about the gods, I am an atheist. But I am an artist too, and therefore a liar. Distrust everything I say. I am telling the truth. The only truth I can understand or express is, logically defined, a lie. Psychologically defined, a symbol. Aesthetically defined, a metaphor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ursula K. Le Guin, The Left Hand Of Darkness&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do As You Will</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/do-as-you-will/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/do-as-you-will/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lock in. Lock in. If you lock in, you can do anything.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Northernlion&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We say it a lot. &lt;em&gt;Do as you will.&lt;/em&gt; Some people interpret it as disapproval, which is a fascinating phenomenon to me. It&amp;rsquo;s not disapproval, not inherently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do we &lt;em&gt;mean,&lt;/em&gt; do as you will? It&amp;rsquo;s simple. Do, as in take action, as you, as in &lt;em&gt;you,&lt;/em&gt; who You are, will, as in the future and the force of will. When I say &amp;ldquo;do as you will,&amp;rdquo; you could interpret that as &amp;ldquo;you can do whatever you want forever,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;re going to do what you&amp;rsquo;re going to do,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;do whatever you decide to do,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;do what you want to.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Ego Death, Murder, &amp; Suicide</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/notes-on-ego-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/notes-on-ego-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quick note: these are loose notes assembled from our thoughts. This is significantly less refined than anything else we&amp;rsquo;ve written.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A lot of people think about &amp;ldquo;ego death&amp;rdquo; as terrifying. There&amp;rsquo;s a line, past which You no longer exist&amp;ndash;of course that&amp;rsquo;s scary, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? It&amp;rsquo;s the void, the unknown. Others who pass it speak of it flippantly, like it wasn&amp;rsquo;t so bad after all, and that&amp;rsquo;s, for some, confusing, for some, terrifying, for some, intriguing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5, 10, and a Little Bit of Magic</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/5n10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/5n10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been talking, right, about writing a spotter&amp;rsquo;s guide to 5&amp;amp;10s for a while, and it hasn&amp;rsquo;t really been &lt;em&gt;flowing,&lt;/em&gt; and that&amp;rsquo;s fine. It&amp;rsquo;s frustrating, admittedly, but that&amp;rsquo;s a me problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was talking, last night, with my colleague, and the topic of writing in general came up, and I said something and then I realized this morning that it&amp;rsquo;d been where I&amp;rsquo;ve gone wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I said, &amp;ldquo;I have a policy, where I do every essay that I can in one go, because if I don&amp;rsquo;t I will never fuckin finish anything.&amp;rdquo; And I realized I had been trying really, really hard to make sure the spotter&amp;rsquo;s guide was &lt;em&gt;perfect.&lt;/em&gt; I&amp;rsquo;d fuckin contacted Ra&amp;ndash;&lt;a href=&#34;https://voidgoddess.org/2023/03/27/demons-from-the-510verse/&#34;&gt;Demons from the 5&amp;amp;10verse!&lt;/a&gt; changed my life&amp;ndash;about maybe picking its brain a little. I was really invested in making it perfect. Yeah, I know, A&amp;rsquo;s a perfectionist, water is wet, bears shit in the woods.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oculis Apertis Somnia</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dream-with-your-eyes-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dream-with-your-eyes-open/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;i-rest&#34;&gt;i: rest.&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;it is what you have been taught. it is what you are learning. it is discovery, slow but sure, of the things inside of you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;things happen, and you respond. those responses carry you onwards. you&amp;rsquo;ll always love the taste of rainwater in the air. that little scar above your eye will fade, later, but you&amp;rsquo;ll remember it, think even after it&amp;rsquo;s gone that you can still see the outline. you&amp;rsquo;ll remember the stories, always, the ones you tell about yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not A Person</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With thanks to Ra, for talking about this in a way that changed my life, and morrigan, for introducing me to its work, amongst other things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://voidgoddess.org/2023/09/26/the-personhood-contract/&#34;&gt;Recommended reading here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personhood is a tool of violence used by Authority, a perpetual threat used to separate Desirables and Undesirables. When any Person considers a group or being Undesirable, they often decry that group or being as not a person, as subhuman, as no better than &lt;em&gt;animals.&lt;/em&gt; You can see this happening&amp;ndash;well, anywhere you look, really, but most definitely in USAmerican politics as we speak.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
