<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>grimoire on Morgan Mayday</title>
    <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in grimoire on Morgan Mayday</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://morganmay.day/grimoire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Ego Death, Murder, &amp; Suicide</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/notes-on-ego-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/notes-on-ego-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A lot of people think about &amp;ldquo;ego death&amp;rdquo; as terrifying. There&amp;rsquo;s a line, past which You no longer exist&amp;ndash;of course that&amp;rsquo;s scary, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? It&amp;rsquo;s the void, the unknown. Others who pass it speak of it flippantly, like it wasn&amp;rsquo;t so bad after all, and that&amp;rsquo;s, for some, confusing, for some, terrifying, for some, intriguing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ego &lt;em&gt;suicide&lt;/em&gt; and ego &lt;em&gt;murder&lt;/em&gt; are concepts plural systems will probably understand more intuitively than singlets. To have an alter kill oneself or another, that&amp;rsquo;s old hat to most anyone in proximity to pop-plur&amp;ndash;even if it hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened in your system, I can almost guarantee it&amp;rsquo;s happened in the system of someone you&amp;rsquo;ve known.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5, 10, and a Little Bit of Magic</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/5n10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/5n10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been talking, right, about writing a spotter&amp;rsquo;s guide to 5&amp;amp;10s for a while, and it hasn&amp;rsquo;t really been &lt;em&gt;flowing,&lt;/em&gt; and that&amp;rsquo;s fine. It&amp;rsquo;s frustrating, admittedly, but that&amp;rsquo;s a me problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I dig into my pancake, take a bite, gesture with my fork and swallow. So I was talking, last night, with my colleague, and the topic of writing in general came up, and I said something and then I realized this morning that it&amp;rsquo;d been where I&amp;rsquo;ve gone wrong.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oculis Apertis Somnia</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dream-with-your-eyes-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dream-with-your-eyes-open/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;i-rest&#34;&gt;i: rest.&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;it is what you have been taught. it is what you are learning. it is discovery, slow but sure, of the things inside of you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;things happen, and you respond. those responses carry you onwards. you&amp;rsquo;ll always love the taste of rainwater in the air. that little scar above your eye will fade, later, but you&amp;rsquo;ll remember it, think even after it&amp;rsquo;s gone that you can still see the outline. you&amp;rsquo;ll remember the stories, always, the ones you tell about yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not A Person</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With thanks to Ra, for talking about this in a way that changed my life, and morrigan, for introducing me to its work, amongst other things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://voidgoddess.org/2023/09/26/the-personhood-contract/&#34;&gt;Recommended reading here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personhood is a tool of violence used by Authority, a perpetual threat used to separate Desirables and Undesirables. When any Person considers a group or being Undesirable, they often decry that group or being as not a person, as subhuman, as no better than &lt;em&gt;animals.&lt;/em&gt; You can see this happening&amp;ndash;well, anywhere you look, really, but most definitely in USAmerican politics as we speak.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
