<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Morgan Mayday</title>
    <link>https://morganmay.day/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Morgan Mayday</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://morganmay.day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 101</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-101/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;See, I say, you&amp;rsquo;ve heard &amp;ldquo;know thy enemy&amp;rdquo;, played some chess, and read &lt;a href=&#34;https://articles.starcitygames.com/articles/whos-the-beatdown/&#34;&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s the Beatdown&lt;/a&gt; and now you have a basic grasp on strategy and tactics. But a &amp;ldquo;basic grasp&amp;rdquo; is only going to get you so far. Welcome to Tactics 101.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;STRATEGY, I write on the whiteboard, and whack it with my marker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Strategy and tactics are not synonymous: this is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; important! Tactics serve strategy, not the other way round. Both inform each other. Just so that we&amp;rsquo;re working with the same definition, let me tell you how strategy works.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;To Strategise, the first step is to identify your GOAL, then OBJECTIVES in service of it. Tactics are how you accomplish those objectives. This is the very simplest understanding I can boil it down to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency, Manipulation, Coercion, and Abuse</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/agency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m cracking the top of my can and sitting down next to you on the stormwall. Listen, honey, I tell you, and shift a bit to get comfortable, to explain this I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to get kinda metaphorical. If you&amp;rsquo;re not in a brainspace for a weird conversation, now&amp;rsquo;s not the time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A lot of people consider manipulation a type of abuse. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re making someone act against their will,&amp;rdquo; well, yes and no. If the magician nudges a card, makes you more likely to pick it when they say &amp;ldquo;any card,&amp;rdquo; is that abusive?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
