<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Morgan Mayday</title>
    <link>https://morganmay.day/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Morgan Mayday</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://morganmay.day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/archives/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey there. Looking for something specific? List below should have it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;general&#34;&gt;General&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/authors&#34;&gt;About the authors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/glossary&#34;&gt;Glossary&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice&#34;&gt;All advice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/tactics&#34;&gt;&amp;hellip; on tactics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/grimoire&#34;&gt;All grimoire pages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;advice&#34;&gt;Advice&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/relationships&#34;&gt;Taking Relationships Seriously, and the Importance of Living Models&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/hacks&#34;&gt;Hacking Yourself Does, Technically, Work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/tactics/000&#34;&gt;Strategy for the Dying Future&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/empathy&#34;&gt;Empathy, People, and You; or, the Flesh Racket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/selfcontrol&#34;&gt;Emotions vs Reason, and Self Control&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/desire&#34;&gt;To Desire&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/beautiful-games&#34;&gt;Beautiful Games&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/apologies&#34;&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t Apologise To Me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/agency&#34;&gt;Agency, Manipulation, Coercion, and Abuse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;-on-tactics&#34;&gt;&amp;hellip; on tactics&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/tactics/000&#34;&gt;Tactics 000&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/tactics/101&#34;&gt;Tactics 101&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/tactics/102&#34;&gt;Tactics 102&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/tactics/300&#34;&gt;Tactics 300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grimoire&#34;&gt;Grimoire&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dream-with-your-eyes-open&#34;&gt;Oculis Apertis Somnia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood&#34;&gt;Not A Person&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking Relationships Seriously, and the Importance of Living Models</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/relationships/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/relationships/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shoutout, as usual, to my colleague morrigan. Most of these thoughts were cohered with or to it last night.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I sigh. &amp;ldquo;Listen,&amp;rdquo; I say, gesture as if I&amp;rsquo;m indicating the puff of heat into the midnight air, &amp;ldquo;you gotta promise not to get weird or attacked, yeah? Cause what I&amp;rsquo;m about to say is&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I ruminate, for a second. &amp;ldquo;Not necessarily objective,&amp;rdquo; I settle on, &amp;ldquo;definitely not &lt;em&gt;nonjudgemental,&lt;/em&gt; but.&amp;rdquo; Shake my head. &amp;ldquo;I judge because I think these are skills that can be learned. I have high standards. That&amp;rsquo;s fine. If I approved of everything unconditionally, my &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/glossary#recognition&#34;&gt;Recognition&lt;/a&gt; would be at best an atrophied mess. If I disapprove, that&amp;rsquo;s not a statement of &amp;lsquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t love you anymore&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t think your thoughts have value&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;I think you&amp;rsquo;re worthless&amp;rsquo;. It just means I think you have room to grow. If you&amp;rsquo;re gonna get weird or attacked about this, now&amp;rsquo;s your chance to leave.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Yourself Does, Technically, Work</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/hacks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I say I&amp;rsquo;m hacking something together, that&amp;rsquo;s a very specific statement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To create something on something else, to patch together a solution from disparate pieces onto an existing workflow, that&amp;rsquo;s something I do all the time in computer science, and every time I do it, I later regret it. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna stop, because it&amp;rsquo;s often the most efficient way for me to learn&amp;ndash;for example, I learned to write Nix by editing .nix files with no fucking clue what I was doing and then parsing the error messages&amp;ndash;but it is bad practices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 000, or: Strategy for the Dying Future</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tactics/000/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I stop laughing, say, &amp;ldquo;no, really,&amp;rdquo; finish pouring my drink and sit down across from you at the kitchen table.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The concept of a probability well is simple. When X type of thing happens, it makes it easier for X type of thing to happen, which makes it easier for X type of thing to happen, which et cetera et cetera et cetera you get the gist.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The example I always use is what I call the &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/glossary#abyss&#34;&gt;Abyss&lt;/a&gt;, the entropic probability well that ends in grey goo or nuclear winter or. The more violence there is, the more violence there is, the more violence there is, fill in whatever kinds of violence ad infinitum. When people talk about a vicious cycle, they&amp;rsquo;re talking about the Abyss.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empathy, People, and You, or: the Flesh Racket</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/empathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/empathy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With thanks, deep and irrevocable, to morrigan.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Required reading: &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood&#34;&gt;Not A Person&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The nature of empathy and sympathy,&amp;rdquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t say, &amp;ldquo;that I&amp;rsquo;ve met very few people who understand, is that they&amp;rsquo;re rarely-to-never going to be exactly right. I don&amp;rsquo;t really think of myself as having sympathy, because sympathy is &lt;em&gt;understanding&lt;/em&gt; how others feel—I can guess, and I can guess very, very well; my models are generally &lt;em&gt;really good&lt;/em&gt;, but I will never be physically inside someone else&amp;rsquo;s head. The mistake of sympathy and empathy is thinking you&amp;rsquo;re always right.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oculis Apertis Somnia</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dream-with-your-eyes-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dream-with-your-eyes-open/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;i-rest&#34;&gt;i: rest.&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;it is what you have been taught. it is what you are learning. it is discovery, slow but sure, of the things inside of you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;things happen, and you respond. those responses carry you onwards. you&amp;rsquo;ll always love the taste of rainwater in the air. that little scar above your eye will fade, later, but you&amp;rsquo;ll remember it, think even after it&amp;rsquo;s gone that you can still see the outline. you&amp;rsquo;ll remember the stories, always, the ones you tell about yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/authors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/authors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;so you want to know who we are. well, we won&amp;rsquo;t tell you that, not outright. make your own judgements.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;but for the sake of simplicity&amp;ndash;a little bit, about each of us, and the site. Essays are tagged by primary author. We all work together, most of the time. If you&amp;rsquo;re careful, and you know us well, you might be able to spot the differences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;morgan&#34;&gt;Morgan&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taskmage, advisor, evoker. Art as a guiding star, passion as an engine, will as a scheme. Something to say on the tip of the tongue. Wild surmise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotions vs Reason, and Self Control</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/selfcontrol/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/selfcontrol/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Association with &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/desire&#34;&gt;To Desire&lt;/a&gt;, amongst other things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The register&amp;rdquo; will require its own whole grimoire page. The working definition for this piece is &amp;ldquo;a tool in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/glossary#cognition&#34;&gt;firmware&lt;/a&gt; layer that logs cognition, allowing for better metacognition.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Minds, broadly, react to stimuli. The human animal reacts to stimuli in one way: thought.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the purposes of this piece, &lt;em&gt;subconscious thought&lt;/em&gt; is any electrical impulse in the brain that results in consequence without being registered in what we call &lt;em&gt;the register.&lt;/em&gt; These most often will be things like ducking at a loud noise, yanking your hand away from a hot stove, or flinching from a blow&amp;ndash;sometimes, you will have them registered, but most of the time, the neuromuscular impulse happens without consulting you. These are things we would consider on the layer of &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/glossary#cognition&#34;&gt;cognitive hardware&lt;/a&gt;&amp;ndash;things that do not bother to be registered, because doing so wastes time that, evolutionarily, not wasting leads to a higher survival rate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Feels Like Shit Checklist</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tools/flschecklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tools/flschecklist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;dt&gt;If you feel like shit, do all of the following you haven&amp;rsquo;t:&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Take your meds&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Have a meal&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Go outside&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Change clothes&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Clean yourself up&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the past couple hours:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Drink water&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Have a snack&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Stretch&lt;br&gt;&#xA;☐ Change scenery&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not A Person</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/personhood/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With thanks to Ra, for talking about this in a way that changed my life, and morrigan, for introducing me to its work, amongst other things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://voidgoddess.org/2023/09/26/the-personhood-contract/&#34;&gt;Recommended reading here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personhood is a tool of violence used by Authority, a perpetual threat used to separate Desirables and Undesirables. When any Person considers a group or being Undesirable, they often decry that group or being as not a person, as subhuman, as no better than &lt;em&gt;animals.&lt;/em&gt; You can see this happening&amp;ndash;well, anywhere you look, really, but most definitely in USAmerican politics as we speak.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Desire</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/desire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/desire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do this&amp;rdquo; is a very simple statement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We live in a world where we have to do things we find unpleasant.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I do not like brushing my teeth. I also have to brush my teeth.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s worse, for a lot of folk in school or assignment-based workspaces. A lot of the time, you have to suffer through boring, routine, difficult but not challenging, or overly challenging tasks, and those &lt;em&gt;suck.&lt;/em&gt; I don&amp;rsquo;t like doing them. They do not bring me joy; this is why I&amp;rsquo;m not currently planning on going back to college.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 300</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/300/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tactics/300/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;This is out of order in the series!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;This is going to be a really dark one. Fair warning. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read the tactics series, they&amp;rsquo;re all under Advice in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/archives&#34;&gt;archives&lt;/a&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;re definitely jumping ahead a bit here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This lesson is about resource denial and losing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In strategy games, a major consideration is resource denial. Any power you take away from your opponents, they cannot bring to bear against you later. Conversely, any power you destroy so they can&amp;rsquo;t have it, you can&amp;rsquo;t have it either. Best-practices resource denial involves denying your opponents resources that you could never use&amp;ndash;you don&amp;rsquo;t raze their fields if you want to take their city, you don&amp;rsquo;t Stone Rain the land you want to Annex next turn, et cetera. Sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s expedient or otherwise necessary to violate best practices, as in almost every arena.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 102</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/102/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tactics/102/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t covered Tactics 101, you should probably go do that &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/articles/tactics-101&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is where things stop being as abstract. In the previous class, I talked about the basics of offense, defense, proactivity, and reactivity. I glossed over opsec and infosec, I quoted Sun Tzu and referenced Machiavelli.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about something different and start getting a little &lt;em&gt;concrete.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;See, today, I&amp;rsquo;m starting with consequences and counterplay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Apologise To Me</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/apologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/apologies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edit 19 Nov 2025: Correction for the unapology, added by Caroline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;Sorry&amp;rsquo; is all well and good, but what are you going to &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; about it?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Let me explain. There are three kinds of apologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One: the &lt;em&gt;superficial apology&lt;/em&gt;. &amp;ldquo;Oop, sorry&amp;rdquo; is the most benign form of this, running into someone and apologising and moving on is, like, just a generally nice thing to do. However, a lot of people extrapolate this into a counterproductive form.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Generally, apologising for something that doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter just obligates the other conversational participants to comfort you. The more self-flagellating the apology, the worse this is, because it carries over into the way I approach other apologies from you in future. If you do something that&amp;rsquo;s, for lack of a better phrase, kinda sucks, I&amp;rsquo;ll point it out to you if I trust you not to self-flagellate about it and just to use the data. If you&amp;rsquo;ve done something that hurts or irritates me, the last thing I&amp;rsquo;m going to want is to have to comfort you out of a spiral. I&amp;rsquo;ll do it, because as a general rule I think that not doing it would be incompatible with who I want to be, but I will not be bringing data to you in future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 101</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tactics/101/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;See, I say, you&amp;rsquo;ve heard &amp;ldquo;know thy enemy&amp;rdquo;, played some chess, and read &lt;a href=&#34;https://articles.starcitygames.com/articles/whos-the-beatdown/&#34;&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s the Beatdown&lt;/a&gt; and now you have a basic grasp on strategy and tactics. But a &amp;ldquo;basic grasp&amp;rdquo; is only going to get you so far. Welcome to Tactics 101.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;STRATEGY, I write on the whiteboard, and whack it with my marker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Strategy and tactics are not synonymous: this is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; important! Tactics serve strategy, not the other way round. Both inform each other. Just so that we&amp;rsquo;re working with the same definition, let me tell you how strategy works.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;To Strategise, the first step is to identify your GOAL, then OBJECTIVES in service of it. Tactics are how you accomplish those objectives. This is the very simplest understanding I can boil it down to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency, Manipulation, Coercion, and Abuse</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/agency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m cracking the top of my can and sitting down next to you on the stormwall. Listen, honey, I tell you, and shift a bit to get comfortable, to explain this I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to get kinda metaphorical. If you&amp;rsquo;re not in a brainspace for a weird conversation, now&amp;rsquo;s not the time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A lot of people consider manipulation a type of abuse. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re making someone act against their will,&amp;rdquo; well, yes and no. If the magician nudges a card, makes you more likely to pick it when they say &amp;ldquo;any card,&amp;rdquo; is that abusive?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gate, of Sorts.</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/spellbook/gate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/spellbook/gate/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/glossary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quick sidebar: all of these are the best working definitions I have to communicate with. Anything marked &amp;ldquo;borrowed from the void&amp;rdquo; is sourced from &lt;a href=&#34;https://voidgoddess.org/void/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. I don&amp;rsquo;t use all terms the same way, so I&amp;rsquo;m just marking the ones I&amp;rsquo;m using verbatim or slightly edited for brevity/interreferentiality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is, for lack of a better term, vibespace. Caveat emptor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-abyss&#34;&gt;The Abyss&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The metaphysical representation of the entropic probability well, the sum of its generals and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
