<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Morgan Mayday</title>
    <link>https://morganmay.day/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Morgan Mayday</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://morganmay.day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/archives/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey there. Looking for something specific? List below should have it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;general&#34;&gt;General&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/authors&#34;&gt;About the authors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/glossary&#34;&gt;Glossary&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice&#34;&gt;All advice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/grimoire&#34;&gt;All grimoire pages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;advice&#34;&gt;Advice&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-300&#34;&gt;Tactics 300&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-102&#34;&gt;Tactics 102&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/apologies&#34;&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t Apologise To Me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-101&#34;&gt;Tactics 101&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/advice/agency&#34;&gt;Agency, Manipulation, Coercion, and Abuse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grimoire&#34;&gt;Grimoire&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dimensions&#34;&gt;Dimensions (unfinished post)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 300</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-300/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-300/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;This is out of order in the series!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;This is going to be a really dark one. Fair warning. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read the tactics series, they&amp;rsquo;re all under Advice in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/archives&#34;&gt;archives&lt;/a&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;re definitely jumping ahead a bit here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This lesson is about resource denial and losing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In strategy games, a major consideration is resource denial. Any power you take away from your opponents, they cannot bring to bear against you later. Conversely, any power you destroy so they can&amp;rsquo;t have it, you can&amp;rsquo;t have it either. Best-practices resource denial involves denying your opponents resources that you could never use&amp;ndash;you don&amp;rsquo;t raze their fields if you want to take their city, you don&amp;rsquo;t Stone Rain the land you want to Annex next turn, et cetera. Sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s expedient or otherwise necessary to violate best practices, as in almost every arena.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 102</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-102/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-102/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t covered Tactics 101, you should probably go do that &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/articles/tactics-101&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is where things stop being as abstract. In the previous class, I talked about the basics of offense, defense, proactivity, and reactivity. I glossed over opsec and infosec, I quoted Sun Tzu and referenced Machiavelli.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about something different and start getting a little &lt;em&gt;concrete.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;See, today, I&amp;rsquo;m starting with consequences and counterplay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/authors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/authors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;so you want to know who we are. well, we won&amp;rsquo;t tell you that, not outright. make your own judgements.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;but for the sake of simplicity&amp;ndash;a little bit, about each of us, and the site. Essays are tagged by primary author. We all work together, most of the time. If you&amp;rsquo;re careful, and you know us well, you might be able to spot the differences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;morgan&#34;&gt;Morgan&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taskmage, advisor, evoker. Art as a guiding star, passion as an engine, will as a scheme. Something to say on the tip of the tongue. Wild surmise.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Apologise To Me</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/apologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/apologies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;Sorry&amp;rsquo; is all well and good, but what are you going to &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; about it?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Let me explain. There are three kinds of apologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One: the &lt;em&gt;superficial apology&lt;/em&gt;. &amp;ldquo;Oop, sorry&amp;rdquo; is the most benign form of this, running into someone and apologising and moving on is, like, just a generally nice thing to do. However, a lot of people extrapolate this into a counterproductive form.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Generally, apologising for something that doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter just obligates the other conversational participants to comfort you. The more self-flagellating the apology, the worse this is, because it carries over into the way I approach other apologies from you in future. If you do something that&amp;rsquo;s, for lack of a better phrase, kinda sucks, I&amp;rsquo;ll point it out to you if I trust you not to self-flagellate about it and just to use the data. If you&amp;rsquo;ve done something that hurts or irritates me, the last thing I&amp;rsquo;m going to want is to have to comfort you out of a spiral. I&amp;rsquo;ll do it, because as a general rule I think that not doing it would be incompatible with who I want to be, but I will not be bringing data to you in future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 101</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/tactics-101/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;See, I say, you&amp;rsquo;ve heard &amp;ldquo;know thy enemy&amp;rdquo;, played some chess, and read &lt;a href=&#34;https://articles.starcitygames.com/articles/whos-the-beatdown/&#34;&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s the Beatdown&lt;/a&gt; and now you have a basic grasp on strategy and tactics. But a &amp;ldquo;basic grasp&amp;rdquo; is only going to get you so far. Welcome to Tactics 101.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;STRATEGY, I write on the whiteboard, and whack it with my marker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Strategy and tactics are not synonymous: this is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; important! Tactics serve strategy, not the other way round. Both inform each other. Just so that we&amp;rsquo;re working with the same definition, let me tell you how strategy works.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;To Strategise, the first step is to identify your GOAL, then OBJECTIVES in service of it. Tactics are how you accomplish those objectives. This is the very simplest understanding I can boil it down to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agency, Manipulation, Coercion, and Abuse</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/advice/agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/advice/agency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m cracking the top of my can and sitting down next to you on the stormwall. Listen, honey, I tell you, and shift a bit to get comfortable, to explain this I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to get kinda metaphorical. If you&amp;rsquo;re not in a brainspace for a weird conversation, now&amp;rsquo;s not the time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A lot of people consider manipulation a type of abuse. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re making someone act against their will,&amp;rdquo; well, yes and no. If the magician nudges a card, makes you more likely to pick it when they say &amp;ldquo;any card,&amp;rdquo; is that abusive?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimensions</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dimensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/grimoire/dimensions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FIRST is WHAT. To exist, you must act. Action is of WHAT. If you can act, you are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SECOND is WHEN. To scry something, it must first exist. Intuition is of WHEN. If you can scry, you are a second-dimensional thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THIRD is WHERE. To find something, you must first scry it. Navigation is of WHERE. If you can locate, you are a third-dimensional thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FOURTH is WHO. To know something, you must first find it. Cognition is of WHO. If you can think, you are a fourth-dimensional thing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/glossary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quick sidebar: all of these are the best working definitions I have to communicate with. Anything marked &amp;ldquo;borrowed from the void&amp;rdquo; is sourced from &lt;a href=&#34;https://voidgoddess.org/void/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. I don&amp;rsquo;t use all terms the same way, so I&amp;rsquo;m just marking the ones I&amp;rsquo;m using verbatim or slightly edited for brevity/interreferentiality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is, for lack of a better term, vibespace. Caveat emptor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Abyss, the: The metaphysical representation of the entropic probability well, the sum of its generals and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
