<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tactics on Morgan Mayday</title>
    <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tactics on Morgan Mayday</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://morganmay.day/tactics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 000, or: Strategy for the Dying Future</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tactics/000/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I stop laughing, say, &amp;ldquo;no, really,&amp;rdquo; finish pouring my drink and sit down across from you at the kitchen table.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The concept of a probability well is simple. When X type of thing happens, it makes it easier for X type of thing to happen, which makes it easier for X type of thing to happen, which et cetera et cetera et cetera you get the gist.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The example I always use is what I call the &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/glossary#abyss&#34;&gt;Abyss&lt;/a&gt;, the entropic probability well that ends in grey goo or nuclear winter or. The more violence there is, the more violence there is, the more violence there is, fill in whatever kinds of violence ad infinitum. When people talk about a vicious cycle, they&amp;rsquo;re talking about the Abyss.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 300</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/300/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tactics/300/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;This is out of order in the series!&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;This is going to be a really dark one. Fair warning. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read the tactics series, they&amp;rsquo;re all under Advice in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/archives&#34;&gt;archives&lt;/a&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;re definitely jumping ahead a bit here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This lesson is about resource denial and losing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In strategy games, a major consideration is resource denial. Any power you take away from your opponents, they cannot bring to bear against you later. Conversely, any power you destroy so they can&amp;rsquo;t have it, you can&amp;rsquo;t have it either. Best-practices resource denial involves denying your opponents resources that you could never use&amp;ndash;you don&amp;rsquo;t raze their fields if you want to take their city, you don&amp;rsquo;t Stone Rain the land you want to Annex next turn, et cetera. Sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s expedient or otherwise necessary to violate best practices, as in almost every arena.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 102</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/102/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tactics/102/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t covered Tactics 101, you should probably go do that &lt;a href=&#34;https://morganmay.day/articles/tactics-101&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is where things stop being as abstract. In the previous class, I talked about the basics of offense, defense, proactivity, and reactivity. I glossed over opsec and infosec, I quoted Sun Tzu and referenced Machiavelli.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about something different and start getting a little &lt;em&gt;concrete.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;See, today, I&amp;rsquo;m starting with consequences and counterplay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics 101</title>
      <link>https://morganmay.day/tactics/101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morganmay.day/tactics/101/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;See, I say, you&amp;rsquo;ve heard &amp;ldquo;know thy enemy&amp;rdquo;, played some chess, and read &lt;a href=&#34;https://articles.starcitygames.com/articles/whos-the-beatdown/&#34;&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s the Beatdown&lt;/a&gt; and now you have a basic grasp on strategy and tactics. But a &amp;ldquo;basic grasp&amp;rdquo; is only going to get you so far. Welcome to Tactics 101.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;STRATEGY, I write on the whiteboard, and whack it with my marker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Strategy and tactics are not synonymous: this is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; important! Tactics serve strategy, not the other way round. Both inform each other. Just so that we&amp;rsquo;re working with the same definition, let me tell you how strategy works.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;To Strategise, the first step is to identify your GOAL, then OBJECTIVES in service of it. Tactics are how you accomplish those objectives. This is the very simplest understanding I can boil it down to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
